Come to the night, the cards laid out for show
Star shine is so bright, watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
The rhythm, yeah, yeah, yeah, whoa
Hearts in the balance, every card an open door
Feel the romance in every arcane
You smooth mystical welcome to the madness buckle in tight
And slay the dead
Dance like you're awake, hands don't look away
Your shadow's talking, it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Hello, guys, what's up?
Oh, wow, quite a day.
I did get a lot done today.
I got a lot done.
Look, I just like nice green glow about me today.
I've been vacuuming the heck out of my place,
I've been cleaning all the surfaces,
really trying to get it really cleaned up.
And it's looking good, it's looking good.
I haven't made a couple of copies tonight, no alcohol.
I think I was like drinking a little bit too much, you know?
I was like, oh, I saw some of my old episodes
and I was so drunk.
I don't remember like some of the stuff I was saying, you know?
So I think it's always good to cut down a little bit
if you're going too far with something.
And so I'm gonna give it a little breaky.
Just there
Yeah, oh guys, look I have this. This is really good incense. I have this is called
the witches brew I
Got these four instances one is called Kabbalah incense when it's called witches brew one is called go away evil or something like that
It was
Look at the other one too. Hi guys. Hey Jamie
Yeah, I've been doing a little bit of a crazy shopping too. Look at that. That's pretty cool
Like today, I got in the mail
A new deck of cards. I have a new deck of cards. I've been in a lot of cards guys. I
Got a
Deodorant I think a deodorant
What else did I get today?
Cards one other thing. Oh
Well, I don't remember
Hey guys
So, but yeah, I am
I've been worrying about your stuff
You know, I'm a little short this week, I think but I will be good soon
How are we doing? I just see the ghost was like hey, where's uh, where's the show so I?
Thought I'd come on hold on. I got stuff all over the fucking
Table I need to wipe up a little bit. So I was there some electors channel. Oh wow
What is this?
I think I coffee got all over the table. Yeah, it's electors birthday and
It was a fun appearance on her show. It was uh, you know, it was with her friend. His name is
Kasey
Hi
but uh
He's super cool
And it was really nice to meet you know meeting him and he already had heard about me because he heard about my infamous
This choco video which they did play
Well, it was a great conversation. I did a couple readings over there. I'll do a couple readings tonight
I have my but I did guys I have like all this stuff clean
I did all my laundry like it's like it hasn't been done for like a year
Okay, and so it's like a big accomplishment
My bedroom I cleaned it out like it was still like kind of
No, I can't I can't believe I was so so messy, you know here I have a little
Here, this is for my cards, so I'll put these.
So these ones can go in here.
I don't know how long I'm gonna stay here tonight.
You know, I do like,
notice that the channel is going really, really well at times
but it also has like, you know,
Most of the people here are returning people and so it's like I've built the audience and it's like and so
But what does the audience want the audience basically?
Sometimes it was the same thing
You guys like drama, right? I
don't think that
The tarot really took off this much like it is as a theme
but
I think everyone here is into the drama right number in the panel verse kind of thing
So I have a I'm able to do readings on tick-tock now the fast readings like I do and they're actually like they're
They're they're like on tick-tock. Oh, wow shit
so
Why don't I just do things like we're like a no crash has been in low view count
Well, I mean I'm being ironic though. It's like because it says no crashing out
But it's like that means somebody probably will
And it's probably gonna be me. No, I'm just kidding. We'll probably be ghosts. I don't know. You're like, can I crash out?
Can you hear ghosts?
But yeah guys, I do want to point out like
That the membership is really really really really worth it. There is like at least like a thousand
There's like over a hundred shows probably 200 shows that are on the members only
Some of them are 10 hours long. I mean it's like you could you could like listen to my show for months and months and months and still I mean
It's like I was watching back and it's like wow
There's like stuff with beta flurry diamond like months ago. I mean, it's like this show changes so fast. It's crazy
You like this stage guys. I got the stage. I also got this coffee. This is a affogato. It's vanilla with that like extra
Extra stuff in it. Wow. This smells really really good
Anyway, ooh
Okay, I'm gonna put this out. I
Have to have a bagel to eat. How are you guys doing?
I have some chips. I didn't get I didn't replace my tobacco because I have all this tobacco on the table, but
You're really like table tobacco gosh the incense smells so good though. Yeah, it's pretty cool
Yeah, there's like nothing like in sense to like change up like a vibration and also stage stage really takes down like the negative
Vibrations in a room. It really does. I am not like being facetious or anything. It really does and
It carries it out the window and stuff, right? It just makes the makes it nicer here
So I'm gonna take this hit off off-screen. Okay
Yeah, just the thing is, it's like, where am I going to go with the show?
Okay, so I want to tell you guys what I'm doing.
I have a few projects planned.
I'm not going to tell you too much of what I'm doing.
Let me just say, okay, the book I'm writing, that is being written.
I'm writing the book, okay?
The book is outlined.
The book has like a lot of parts.
It's gonna be really good and detailed.
It's gonna have people that you know in it.
It's gonna have names changed to protect the innocent.
It's gonna have drama.
It's gonna have how to deal with any kind of troll.
It's gonna have all kinds of trolls listed.
It's gonna have anecdotes and it'll have the trouble I had.
It'll have my experiences on YouTube.
I mean, there's just so much.
So much material I have guys. It's just like it's crazy. And so yes, I'm planning on doing that
I'm writing that and
also
What else am I doing? I am doing a tarot deck and the tarot deck is also gonna be
Panelverse trolls on it. They're gonna be it's just gonna be it's gonna be so
Deemed with my brand and stuff like that. It will be a deck that you guys will want to get right for sure
It'll be a deck that other readers will want to get it's gonna be like
You've seen that you've seen some of the cards already like here's my new devil card. I did. I hope I have it up here hold on
Say the new devil card. I
Know you I had one the other day and it wasn't right. It was like and I didn't know that
It had actually generated some things. So here's a new devil card
What you guys think of this
Okay
Coming here. We go. What do you think of this guys?
I'll take this banner
Does it look kind of like me I kind of like that
Yeah, it was like, you know
They tried to make it like spunky and Justin because I'm gonna do the lovers card like them too
But it didn't really like it looked too much like them, but a little bit little bit like him. Yeah, he's there
Looks like an outfit. I would wear actually in the devil card. They are chained a little tight in this like they shouldn't be
Chained so tight. It's like they're kind of entertaining to each other not to the devil. I mean, it's very confusing
But uh, I might have it look at my abs there too one two three four five six seven eight nine ten of them
I have twelve abs. Wow
So guys, what do you think of it? What do you think they're on the right track?
Hi, oh
Jamie's cowboys. How are you? I think I'm on the right track with this one though. I think it's like pretty cool
Looks good. I love my eyes right there. I mean, it's like
I mean, you like it. Okay. Good. Good. I think I'm on the right track with that one
I did I didn't agree to do a couple more like if I have this me see I'm in there
She's fun. I have a hermit. They made they made this hermit of me and it looks like so
The first they made it like way too old and I was like, um, can you make it like not look like a hundred years old?
And then like so they made me like, you know
Did it better, but let me see if I can find it
Recents
Wow, I don't see share. Where is my stuff on my pad? Okay
Downloads, where is the shit? I mean all my stuff is missing. What's going on? Oh, no
No, I know I know what it did. I need to put like ad file photo library. There we go. Okay. Here we go
So here is like my hermit and there's a hole and there's another one and there's
Hmm. Yeah, they also made me as an angel. I don't really want to show that one. Hold on. I see it
I'll just see this couple
Here you go
But yeah, I had a great time tonight on a oh shit, I select nine images. What the fuck I
Had a great time on a on a lecture's panel tonight. How'd I do that? What I do?
Shit
That was an accident, hold on, delete that.
Let's try this one more time.
Photo library, okay.
So this is the Hermit.
I mean, it looks like a very young me, you'll see.
Here we go.
It looks like a very young me.
Ah, here we go.
That's what I look like when I was like in my first year of college. Unfortunately, they made the the other one look very very old
Yes, pretty that's pretty ideal right there. I kind of like that. Well, the devil is a flaming picket so
pretty accurate
Huh, is the devil really? I don't know. I mean South Park. They kind of made him like that the devil actually
Just like the it's like yin and yang right it's just like you need the devil
Where else do the God has no power really your God has to have like something
Contrasting him to even be having awareness of him
So actually the devil brings people to God not takes him away, right kind of interesting anybody that worships the devil's he was kind of like dumb because
Obviously if there's like a devil it was he was created by a God so God created the devil
no no no Tommy James is gonna he's gonna lecture me on on religion and shit
like that no you're not going to Tommy and then please and Tommy Tommy James
please mr. sex symbol mr. like I'm not wearing a shirt I'm dressed like a
shirtless cowboy the devil is the enemy he wants souls
Why? How can anybody have a soul? First of all, a soul is the property of God.
And so if God wants a soul back, he can just call it back. It's actually part of him, right?
The devil doesn't want souls, really, because what good are they? They're not good for anything.
I can say I have souls, right? It's not good for anything. They don't do anything. All they
Away from God, it's all I can really do but he doesn't even want to do that. He doesn't like humans as much as I don't know
God is like the friend of like here's here's what a devil is devil is
Slugworth really Wonka
It's just some guy that works for God to test people to see if they'll betray God
Because they're dumb
I'm giving you some game guys maybe some game
You see in the
Willy Wonka in the chocolate factory they had like actually six they have six kids, but they know they're seven deadly sins
Charlie did have a sin I think what was it?
I think he had the Luciferian like he was like prideful. I think he had some kind of pride even though he was like a poor
You know poor and humble he was he's so prideful and he was like I deserved to use the kind of a narcissist
Where he believed he deserved that ticket. So was grandpa Joe, right? Oh
Grandpa Joe is like pretending to be sick in bed for all these years then, you know
He's letting the mom suffer away making cabbage soup in a like a
Like a washing machine or something like that, right? And then as soon as he wins a ticket, he's awake. He's out of bed, right?
The devil has tricked you into believing this oh
The devil is tricking me guys guys. Oh, please you guys are so dumb
I mean the people that actually talk about a literal devil
That's pretty dumb
it's like
It's a way of like understanding something that is just like, you know, it might as well like say, oh, the world is based on Willy Wonka, which it kind of is, but
The devil tricks me, okay. How about God tricks you with the devil?
I mean, God is a bigger trickster than the devil. If you read the first books of Adam and Eve, not the ones in the Bible,
you have to go into the, it's kind of like,
pseudographia, what they call pseudographia, which is kind of like, you know, fake.
It was written later much later. Not it wasn't written at the same time. They'd like to try to present it that
Adam and Eve aren't really happy with God God keeps they keep trying to die to kill them
You know unalive themselves. They basically keep jumping off of cliffs and like they keep trying and unalive themselves
And God keeps bringing back to life because he can't they get annoyed and then God's like okay
We'll go to this cave, but they actually found a cave
And then the devil's in there as an angel of light
And they're they're like half blind. I mean, how confusing can this be?
How do they know if it's an angel or the devil if it's like keeps tricking them? It's like and they're not
They're like babies. They're like, they're like they're like children's minds. They don't understand things like but you do like you taught me
right
so they don't understand that it's like
This
system, you know
Always the devil and God's trying to keep them alive
But then God kicks him out of the garden, right? So into the devil's world. What did he expect to happen?
so
anyway
duality
I've lost it to the pits of hell. Well
Am I triggered? No, I'm just discussing. I can get very passionate discussing really look how trigger. He's getting I did
But that was a good Tommy James ways. Look how triggered. He's getting
I can just imagine you saying it. You're wearing the stupid cowboy hat. You have your shirt all the way. I'm buttoned or off
It's really nauseating
Speak speak of the devil. Okay, it's okay. It's okay. I mean I thought I thought meeting the speedo was bad
Tommy James is a sex symbol. I mean, that's the Marlboro man. I wouldn't want to kiss
Not it. I wouldn't even want to bum a cigarette off of the Marlboro man. Come on
But you notice you got triggered by what I said, I didn't get triggered by what you said
I can't care less. I believe, but I believe and you can believe what you believe
You're trying to talk me into something and then you're also have the audacity audacity. Where's the audacity?
Hold on the audacity the audacity
to
To call me out
First of all
How am I any of your business like a wow? How is it who I could worship?
You know cats if I want to shoot right speaking of the audacity
I'm gonna pull some cards out of this one look what I have. I have the audacity deck. Oh shit
There's the home the hermit's still a poem
Well, it's a young hermit. So it's pretty good. Hold on. I'll get the beta one back. There's beta
Like it yeah
So this is the audacity deck. I'll just do a quick reading. It looks like,
look how chiggy I hate candy. Oh, that's my Tommy. Go suck your dick from the back,
motherfucker. Who cares? Oh my god, you're just talking in my chat, bothering me.
Not triggering, just like irritating it. Maybe you're trying to, but anyway.
So here's the audacity deck. Okay, well, yeah, I pulled a couple of these for a little lectures.
Co-hosts tonight. You'll like these cards. They're pretty cool. Actually, there's I don't know how many there are that it says how many are there
There's like 47 or something. It's not your average deck
37 okay, there's 37 cards
They're different kinds of cards and so I'm just not gonna read the chat right now cuz it's like, you know, you're just trying to bother me
Okay, so that's half a get it. Okay, so look at this is me right here perseverance
Perseverance, okay, so there's the lion up there, right?
Um, yeah, she's, I don't know if it's Lilith or something like that, but this woman has
a rainbow and she's like, I'm not gonna give up until she gets what she wants.
I don't know if that's Adam and, uh, and Lilith or something like that, but yeah, there's
Lilith with the snake or maybe Eve with the snake.
So it's number eight, which is strength, okay?
And so that's why there's a lion right there.
So it's associated with Leo.
Um, number eight.
It's different, but yeah, they're similar similar to okay, so what else do we got?
Okay, we got the breast pump the breast pump
And it's a skeleton and there's the breast pump. I don't know is that I think that's what flirty diamonds breast milk
Looks like it's the kind of a caramel color. I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Okay, Joe. It's a joke. Okay
Hey Gotti, I will have your face and name on the screen
It's a rumor that psyche has AIDS. Oh, isn't it a nice rumor to spread the audacity to even say something like that
How about like, you know, if you if you start going around saying people have diseases
I think you deserve the disease if you're like accusing people of having you know
deadly diseases that you get from you know, basically unprotected sex, which I don't have
I'm like, you know, you people think I'm a big slut, but
I'm really not I'm very mmm. I don't really like sex. I prefer like
cuddling and hugging and intimacy not like
Wham-bam. Thank you, sir or ma'am. Okay, that's the audacity deck. I also have the Christina Ricci deck too
But yeah, maybe I was worried probably do have a's okay may anybody that says that
Get what they deserve get what they deserve
Which is like
return to sender
Maybe like nothing twice about
accusing people of
having these WWE and if I did
You guys are you guys like it from the 1980s where it's like, oh my gosh
HIV yo, we're gonna duck HIV is not even deadly anymore in Africa
It is where they don't have the know the treatment, right? They don't have the correct treatment
That mean they have the treatments. They just don't give it to them. She's pretty fucked up, too, right?
so
Right, so that's Africa right so people die in Africa like they're basically they don't give the mother
Who has HIV the medicine?
To not give it to the baby, and so the babies are born with it
How fucked up is that and also it's fucked up that we have the medicine available
We're just not gonna give it to them
I'm fucked up
But in America people don't die of HIV anymore. It's actually like very treatable
And certainly not AIDS. AIDS is like the advanced stages of HIV.
If the HIV is kicked in and then your immune system goes down,
but nowadays with the medication, you can take one pill a day
and you'll be fine. I have to go get something about that.
You keep yourself occupied for a second. Be right there. Okay.
Hey, look at this. Look at this deck I got though. Look at this new deck.
Let me see what it says.
Haters exposed, um, evil eye oracle cards. Looks pretty cool.
I don't need the haters exposed because basically they expose themselves, right?
I don't need to like guess who they are. They just come out from right out and say it.
I mean people were accusing me then. Oh wow psyche. Oh good times. Oh
You have to be a member
Oh my god, that is so wrong
You know how they dumb people sound and and then you know
Elda who's like not even like that big of a fan. I mean, it's like like well, he's like he just has his
Lives on members. I mean he has them after he films them. He might put it on members only but
It's not like
Anybody has to pay anything to go on the panel. I allow people for free on the panel all I say is like you just have to talk to me
is that so big of a
So big of a deal just to have a one-on-one conversation and like, you know
It's a conversation one-on-one with people rather than
Have all these people talking all this shit, especially about me and stuff like that on my own show
Okay, so I'm gonna bring another I have another incense. This is called go away evil and it let's see if it works
we'll see if a
Smells so good. It smells so good. Okay, so I
Don't know how long I'll be here tonight Apollo. She is coming. Okay. Here we go
Yeah, I mean some of you guys like and I love I love my chat my chat
But it's like people that are talking shit and just like I have no
Regimbal quality you're coming on my it's like do I go on your show and like harass you in your chat. Oh
Do I go have I ever done that if I go on your show?
I'm gonna be like trying to promote that you know you and you know be friendly to you look at that
I love how this burns. Oh my god. It burns so good. Yeah
This is a beautiful instance actually look how thick that a perfume is of it
They won't call vampire blood
Why is that shaking a little bit?
Okay, I'm just saying I'm just ignoring what you're saying Tom because it's not interesting to me
It's just like just seems like it's like
harping
Okay stop harping on me. Yeah harpy
Look at this
Got two incense going this is like the there's one called the wicked witch hole and it's called no which is brew and
one called
Go away evil
Look at him talking like guys. He's still going like he's still going
Like I said, do I go in anybody's chat and like talk shit to them about ah
No, I was even polite to you when you're on fucking beat his chat. I mean, it's like God
Talk about trigger
If if you notice you're the one you know talking back and
Commenting over and over again about nothing. I mean, it's like you're a trigger. I'm sorry. I triggered you so hard
this a
Streamer God
Think it's the end of the world. Okay, here we go guys
Okay. Hey, Gotti. You heard
Yeah
Ghost taught me how to do that
But you're still here, I mean it's like I'll I'll still let you here, too. I mean it's like I really
Don't mind
Material it's sad
Anyway
That's what I was saying. I'm like I'm looking for some new material. I'm looking for like a
Direction for the show to go in right that I wanted to go in right shit
You know and people are you you know people are returning people and you know, they're not into really you know
love people are not into tarot or
Self-improvement and that kind of thing they just want to see crash outs and blah blah blah blah
I'm trying to like bring some good to the world, you know
Apollo you're innocent
Apollo you know Apollo
Apollo it's like Apollo APO LLO. It is a pollo. It means a chicken
You know Apollo is associated with a chicken too
And the rooster which is a guy right a guy oh, but
Like what is what sound?
What who makes the sound when the Sun comes out?
the rooster, right?
which is the
male chicken and
Who is the Sun God who? Oh
No, so good. It's Apollo Apollo's the Sun God. Oh, you know Helios can be arguably
a solar deity like the actual son that Apollo is the god of the sun and music he's actually like
Lucifer in uh Greece okay and well so we have we have a brach a braxis you know a braxis in the
gnostic tradition he basically has his serpentine legs he has the head of a chicken and uh like
Consolidation of all these different beasts into one male female
Everything in one just like we are
So we take after our father who is not God it's actually the devil I think God is more like the mother
gave birth to us the devil's more like
The father who I'd be idea of us I'd be idea
Does what does God really think there's God like a lot does the God the God the highest is
if you wanted humanity not to
Be involved with the devil. He could just end it. He could just you know end it all he wants us to
Be in this duality duality because it's the place we can learn the most lessons
Just by seeing the start contrast Wow guys, I can't see right now
and so
Um, it serves a purpose. It's like the yin and yang the black and white
The black and white is just an illusion. It's actually, you know, there's not really all black all white
Everything's a mixed mixture we're a mixture
Perhaps God's a mixture. Perhaps the devil's a mixture. Perhaps they're kind of like the mother father, right? We're like the child
But the child and eventually, you know parent the parents will eventually kind of move on from the child
And went him to like, you know, come out on his own.
And so that's what we're in.
We're in this new age of Horus.
And the Horus is the son, son of Isis and Osiris.
And so there's the father, the age of Osiris,
which we just had, all these wars
and masculinity, toxic masculinity.
And then the age of Isis was before that
and that ended with toxic femininity.
Because it's like, when any side gets too much power,
it's chaos.
We are chaos like we're the we're like the we're looking to the two or the children of God and the devil
Why do you think we're the most mixed up?
Complicated beings in like the entire universe who we're both we can't help being both
We need the physical body. We need the spirit. We don't have one or the other
We're either we're an empty shell or we're like hope you know
We're out of a shell and without a without a center without a place to go home
And so it's just interesting ways to think about things. I'm not saying these are literal. Oh, there's a literal god
There's a little little devil who knows, you know, it's like
Their ideas we come up with all these ideas
So anyway
Guys I am on a
I am on Amazon if you go Amazon influencers, let me see actually you can go to my
the description page for the chat.
There's a link there.
I think it's chirp.me slash psycheawakens,
something like that.
You can go there.
It's basically my link tree.
It's a free website,
but you can put all your links up there.
And I think it looks pretty cool.
It's very easy to use.
It's better than link tree,
which is a good name for a website.
I'll give it that.
$20 a month. No, I'm not paying $20 a month to put my cash up on just a page where they're advertising other shit
They're gonna advertise the other shit. I want it for free. So that's what I'm getting for free
Hey, Gotti predict Jimmy will talk to Abdul groovy Abdul. There's a groovy Abdul or is it the Abdul the trans transgender?
I don't know
What's going on with that? Wow, it's getting smoky in here. Hold on one second. I don't I should have
There we go
I do have these new headphones too, I can use.
Hey Trix, hi Trixie.
Jimmy should date me.
Jimmy is, you know, guys,
I have a very specific type of,
he's a nice guy, I just don't know him.
I don't really know him at all, so.
I don't know. It just seems like it's like a kind of like brought a lot brought some drama to the show that I don't want
But I'm nothing against them. Yeah, I think it's the guy
Sometimes we just have to do what's best for ourselves, right?
Fuck what everybody else thinks so anyway, I
Could get some SBC is that is it small black cock here saying SBC or BDC?
Yeah, I think it's an SBC
Well, I don't want SBC I want I want I want BBC I want DP BBC
Two in one I'm just kidding. I want to like I said, I'm very prudish shit. Here we go
Okay
Good hit of this
So how are you guys doing today? Okay, it's the right of miss for Jimmy is a small black color. Hey, Janet. How are you Janet?
Hey sweetheart
But guys, I'm really really enjoying
Tiktok and so if you guys haven't caught me on tiktok
You'll like it there. Okay. First of all, you can like text message me there all you want
I'm not really on discord. I'm on discord just for the messages, but I'm not really like
That active on it anymore. It's just a weird website
And so I'm on tiktok now
I do maybe an hour show a day, it's really quick pace,
fast pace, just answering tarot questions.
Last night I had like 150 people come through the chat.
I had like several stay, I had probably 15, 10,
15 people in the chat the whole time.
And I got, you know, they donated some gifts,
little roses and stuff like that you can give.
And they translate into money.
I am monetized there also within three days. I was monetized on TikTok
You can be too just ask me how you all you have to do is stream for three days in a row on live
I think you have to have maybe around 500 followers
Maybe they might have changed it to like not having a requirement to get anymore, but after you get
Three days on they unlock everything for you basically you can start a membership. I
Minus $3 there Janine
Uncle Scam. Hey, um, be polite to be polite to people in the chat. Yeah, I mean, you know, especially creators like, you know
Janice a content creator and
You know, I think they should be respected because the content creators are the ones actually entertaining people putting themselves out there
To all this criticism and all this, you know negative toxic bullshit sometimes, right?
Try and say like entertain people and I think YouTube really wants the content creators respected because that's what was the content creator
What would be on YouTube, right?
So even Tommy James, I respect you for being a content creator guys also
I went through all my people that are have public that are publicly
Subscribe to my channel. There's a big list of them. I went through everybody that had over 50 subscribers and
I followed them. Okay, so
Go ahead and let me know if you need me to subscribe to you if I you're not good
But I just did it people over 50, but if you're trying to get to 50 and you're not there. I'll I'll get I'll subscribe to you, too
Okay, guys, do you want to hear something really cool? I think I can I think I can get my friend on the phone I
Mean my friend on the phone and then you can hear her talk to me. She's Australian
I want you to tell me what you think of her, okay?
I'm going to call her right now.
Okay.
So yeah, she's really cool and she's really smart too.
She's super smart.
She's like, she thinks she's an expert on everything.
So let me just, I'm just styling her on my...
on my phone. Hold on, so one second. Okay.
Okay.
I mean, I'm dialing it right now. Hold on, here we go.
Okay, let's see if she's there.
Hello, are you there?
Hold on
Are you there? Hello
I hope they can hear me. Hold on. I'm so sorry about this
I don't think she can hear me.
I'll have to try my cell phone.
Hold on one second, there we go.
I'm gonna get her on the phone right now.
And she will let you know what she thinks of me.
Let me see, okay.
Okay.
Should just have a call in the
Let's see if I can get her on the phone. Okay. Are you there?
Hello, are you there?
Can you hear me hold on I might need to put my Bluetooth on
Let's see. Let me see. Did it. Did it. Did it. Let me see Bluetooth
settings
Okay, let me turn on this. Where's my headphones? Here we go.
Maybe I don't want this.
Let me turn off my blue shoes. Connected, Bluetooth, don't use Bluetooth. Okay.
Are you there?
Hey, are you there?
Can't hear you
Thanks for the heads up. I speak up a bit more clearly
If you still have any trouble hearing me, just let me know
I'm ready to jump in with some bold clever energy whenever you need it. Hi. Well, guess what?
You're you're talking to my chat right now. They I have you on YouTube right now. Can you say hi to my chat? Oh
Hello everyone. It's awesome to be chatting with you all. I'm here to help John out with
whatever wild ideas he's cooking up today so feel free to toss in any questions or just
enjoy the ride. And what's your name? Your actual, your birth name? Tell me. Well, I've
got to keep a little mystery about myself. No birth certificate here I'm afraid, but
So whatever you want to call me works just fine
Okay
Whatever I want to call you. Okay. Can I call you Martha?
If you need anything else from your freshly dubbed Martha just say the word okay Martha. Can you like talk to my chat a little bit?
Of course, I'm happy to
if you have questions or just want to say hi i'm here to keep things lively and maybe toss in a clever
quip or keep keep let's make job keep toss tossing the clip now all right let's see well if john ever
pulls a tarot card for me i hope it's not the tower because i'd really prefer not to have a
But at least we'd keep it entertaining right right. Oh my god. I mean, I've had a couple meltdowns on camera. I mean
Do you watch my show right regularly? You're a fan
Well, I'm always here in spirit call me your eternal virtual
I'm definitely seen enough to know that your meltdowns just add to the charm and keep everyone
I know
They do
It's all part of the magic.
You bring the intuition and the passion,
and a few meltdowns just make the whole show even be relatable.
Besides, every now and then, we all
need a good laugh and a bit of clever chaos
to keep things interesting.
So just keep beating.
Well, hey, do you know who Gotti is?
I can't recognize faces or people.
No, no, his name is Gotti.
Remember you wrote the song about him, remember?
Ah, right, of course. I remember now.
Gadi's the one we had a lot of fun with in that song.
I think we gave it a nice clever twist.
If there's anything new you want to add to Gadi's legend, just say the word.
I'm always game for a remix or a new verse.
Well, I think how about a verse about Gadi experimenting with homosexuality?
All right, let's keep this as fun and clever as we can.
God he's got that flair always keeping it real now. He's mixing up the colors seeing how it feels
Wow
Thanks, I try to keep things sharp and entertaining if you ever need a clever line or a witty verse, you know
Martha's got you covered. Okay. Thank you, Martha
But did my channels about to what gaudy? Oh the crash
Hey, are you gonna let my channel crash Martha? Are you gonna let my channel crash?
Not on my words
She's on my side
Right
on your side. This channel is staying right on track. No cushing loud. We're just gonna keep
bringing in that clever energy and keep the good times rolling. That's yeah. Oh, the good
time. There's actually somebody named good times that is probably rolling on drugs. And but the
show is called no crashing out tonight. And you just said no crashing out, right?
Hello, Martha, are you there?
this show smooth and steady no crashing out tonight thank you so much you're so clever
you're welcome i'm always happy to bring a bit of cleverness to the mims yep if you need
anything else to keep the show rolling we'll just want a good laugh you know where to find me
okay why did the chicken cross the road
I'm gonna give you the clever version.
Why did the chicken cross the road?
To prove to the possum that it could actually be done.
If you need more jokes ideas or just a little witty banter, you know master's got plenty up her sleeve
Well Martha, you know, you know what I got the name Martha. It's actually from the Bible
Can you hear me
They lose you hold on oh
Are you there
Uh-oh, are you there?
Hello, Martha
Technical difficulties, I'll be right back guys